THE HUSBAND
THIS SERIES IS FICTITIOUS
CHILDREN WERE FILMED SAFELY
GEN AI WAS USED IN SELECT SCENES
To pick up the money.
What? Money?
The three billion you have here.
I need you to hand it over to me.
Let Seyun go first.
Then I'll give you the money.
No, Mother.
Give me the money first.
That's the only way she'll live.
What?
You greedy bastard.
[suspenseful music playing]
Here's your money as promised.
For real this time.
You've gotten pretty smart, Mr. Kang.
All right, Mr. Kang.
Why don't we talk this out?
At 8 p.m. tonight,
wait in front of Dong Nam Sports Center.
I'll tell you the exact location then.
Where do I meet you?
[Manhui] Mr. Kang.
Come to Do San Development Company.
You have 10 minutes.
Is this the police?
EPISODE 9
EMERGENCY SERVICES, AMBULANCE
-[Dosik] Hey, Choi.
-Yes, sir.
[Hyeonsu] This way.
[breathing heavily]
[Dr. Ko] Critical?
These people are criminals
that did horrible things to my daughter.
How could I let them in my hospital?
You, say something.
Have you forgotten what you've done?
You orchestrated the hit on my daughter,
you broke into my home with a gun
and took three billion won from me.
STYLE
::cue()
You really think you have
any right to be in this room?
Well, I took the money for a reason.
I couldn't tell you at the time.
I was planning to give it back
as soon as I got Seyun back.
Then where's my three billion?
Let me see it now!
I put it in my trunk.
[Dr. Ko] What?
I put it in the trunk
of the car I was driving.
-[Dosik] Check the trunk.
-Yes, sir.
[Dosik] Honestly,
I still don't know what to believe.
Whether you were actually
trying to save your wife,
or you just ended up saving her
when things went sideways.
Let's say you're telling the truth.
But what about the money?
Where is that three billion?
I told you. I left it in the trunk.
We searched the whole thing
but found nothing.
So be honest with us, Mr. Kang.
If what you said were true,
the money would've been in the trunk.
We don't know what else we'll find,
so search every inch.
[Hyeonsu] Yes, sir.
What's that?
It's a cell phone.
It was under the fridge.
-[Dosik] The fridge?
-Yeah.
[Hyeonsu] Captain.
You should see this.
COME TO THE HOSPITAL
WE NEED TO TALK
[Dosik] "To the hospital"?
-Is that all?
-Yeah, everything else was wiped clean.
[sighs] Get Kim Gyeongae's phone
to Forensics now.
And track down the owner of this number.
What?
Kang Taeju was there?
Why are you telling me this now?
I'll take care of it myself.
Just come to the hospital.
Darn, Kang Taeju.
If only he hadn't shown up.
[phone buzzing]
INCOMING CALL
[buzzing continues]
[phone buzzes]
PROCEED AS PLANNED
[sighs]
[phone buzzes]
MESSAGES
NEW MESSAGE
[tense music playing]
Honey.
Hang in there.
THE HUSBAND
STYLE
::cue()
FORENSICS
POLICE
POTASSIUM CHLORIDE
NS: NEUROSURGERY
HA JEONGSOO
DO NOT CROSS, POLICE LINE
UNDER INVESTIGATION
[indistinct radio chatter]
You came down here, looking for
Ha Jeongsoo and called his phone,
you heard his phone ringing
by the emergency stairs,
and found him collapsed there.
Is that correct?
[Taeju] Yeah, that's correct.
[Dosik] But why were you
looking for him anyway?
[footsteps approaching]
What… Is it true?
Dr. Ha is dead?
Yes.
I need to see him myself.
[stammers]
Forensics is in there right now.
You're not allowed.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
[Dr. Ko] How did Dr. Ha end up…
What in the world happened?
-We're looking into that right now.
-[Dr. Ko sighs]
Director Ko should be able to tell you
a lot more about Dr. Ha than I can.
[mysterious music playing]
He was going to meet Dr. Ha last night.
Is that correct?
I… Well…
He called out of the blue last night
about an emergency,
so I came to the hospital like he asked.
But when I arrived, I couldn't find him.
I couldn't reach him either,
so…
I went back home after a while.
What?
What are you saying?
[scoffs] Calm down.
I can't understand a word!
[sighs]
You know what a huge problem
you've caused?
Where are you right now?
No. Just come back to the hospital!
[gasps]
-[phone buzzes]
-[Dosik] Detective Oh. Yeah, got it.
I'm going to check
the surveillance footage.
Give me a minute.
[gasps] I'll go with you.
Be right back.
[music intensifies]
[music ends]
STYLE
::cue()
This is the parking garage last night.
SECTOR A
And this is after Mr. Ha walked past.
First comes Director Ko.
This is the parking area.
Next comes Mr. Kang.
-Yeah, it's just like Mr. Kang said.
-Right.
And this is Mr. Ha taking the elevator
up to the hospital.
MAIN BUILDING E/V #3
[no audible dialogue]
[Dosik] Hold on.
Did he go right back down?
[Detective Oh] Yeah.
Who was that on the elevator with him?
Dr. Cha Myeonghui.
To be honest,
I was a bit stunned when I got the call.
I had no idea that Dr. Ha
would do anything like that.
So, you were on the elevator
with him last night, correct?
Yes.
Would you mind telling us
what you guys talked about?
I said hi to him,
but he didn't say anything.
He didn't look so well,
so I asked if he was okay.
So, what did he say?
He just said he was fine.
But something was off about him.
It sounded like he was
talking to himself under his breath.
Talking to himself?
Do you know what he was saying?
Uh…
I didn't quite make out
what he was saying.
I just told him to come to me
if he's struggling.
That's all I could do for him.
I had no idea that would be the last time.
Well, do you happen to know
why he took the same elevator down
to the basement?
No, I got off before that,
so I don't know.
[Dosik] Right. Of course.
So what was he like on an average day?
Anything peculiar?
It's hard to say for sure
since we never had a formal consultation.
But the past few times
I ran into him recently,
he did seem a bit on edge.
I wouldn't say he was anxious,
but like he had a lot
weighing on his mind.
All right.
And thank you for your time.
I'll let you know if I remember
anything that might help.
You can call me anytime.
Yeah, we appreciate it.
STYLE
::cue()
MAJOR CRIMES UNIT 2
[Detective Oh] You're back.
Captain, we got the autopsy results.
SUSPECT PROFILE
NAME: KIM GYEONGAE
[suspenseful music playing]
CARDIAC ARREST FROM
POTASSIUM CHLORIDE INJECTION
[exhales deeply]
Captain, I think you should see this.
What is it?
About the phone
that Ha Jeongsoo had on him…
Yeah.
It's the same number
that contacted Kim Gyeongae.
-What?
-And here.
They texted each other
on the date of Ms. Ko Seyun's abduction.
SEONGJIN POLICE STATION
[Dosik] Why were you looking for Mr. Ha?
I had to ask him something.
Ask him what?
Kim Gyeongae…
Why he tried to kill her.
He tried to kill her?
What do you mean by that?
Two nights ago,
I found him in her room and he had
a vial of potassium chloride in his hands.
Potassium chloride?
I barely stopped him from injecting it
into her IV without dilution.
[mysterious music playing]
COME TO THE HOSPITAL
WE NEED TO TALK
[Dosik] This message is from the phone
we found on Mr. Ha Jeongsoo.
He sent it to Kim Gyeongae
on the day your wife was abducted.
It seems he used this phone
only for contacting her.
Mr. Ha was keeping her
updated on your movements, Mr. Kang.
What's wrong?
Dr. Ha told me that day at the hospital
that he was only…
doing as he was told.
[Dosik] "Doing as he was told"?
You mean someone else
put him up to kill Kim Gyeongae?
That's what I'm not sure about.
I went back
to the hospital to find that out.
[music ends]
[monitor beeping]
Ms. Kim.
Ms. Kim? Can you hear me at all?
Yeah.
-[groans]
-[knocks on door]
[sliding door opens]
[Dosik] How's it going?
-Hi.
-How's she looking?
She's regained consciousness,
but she's still a bit out of it.
Ms. Kim Gyeongae?
We're with the police.
[stammers]
This thing is a bit uncomfortable.
You're currently under arrest.
And your husband is a wanted man.
Ms. Kim, why did you kidnap Ms. Ko Seyun?
Ms. Kim.
What was the purpose
of kidnapping Ko Seyun?
Detective? The patient has
just regained consciousness.
She needs rest
more than anything right now.
Maybe you should continue another time.
[monitor beeping continues]
-Fair enough.
-Thank you.
Both my husband and I…
we were just pawns in this game.
[eerie music playing]
An update on
the major hospital kidnapping case.
-Kidnapping?
-Police investigation has revealed
that a doctor at the facility,
identified as Suspect B,
ordered accomplice A
to kidnap the hospital chairwoman,
-the director's daughter.
-My gosh.
Suspect B was reportedly struggling
with multi-million-won private debt,
STYLE
::cue()
and police now believe he took
his own life after the plot failed.
Gosh, I feel so bad for Dr. Kang.
The police were after him for days
when he was innocent.
He looked like he had
wounds all over his body too.
See? I told you.
I said, Dr. Kang would never do
something like that, didn't I?
But can you believe that about Dr. Ha?
We used to see him every day here.
He seemed so gentle.
But he was up to something so horrible?
I mean, he made a lot of mistakes,
so I just thought he was a bit clumsy.
Guess you can never really know someone.
You're such a bad judge of character.
I always knew he was trouble.
That look in his eyes was…
You know, he always seemed a bit on edge.
Like he was nervous.
The investigation into the high-profile
hospital kidnapping case,
which shocked the public,
has taken a major turn.
Suspect A, who has regained
consciousness after surgery,
reportedly testified to police
that they followed Suspect B's orders.
Meanwhile, Dr. Kang,
who was once named a suspect…
[doorbell rings]
…has suffered from an overreaching
police investigation. Consequently--
FRONT DOOR
SAVE, OPEN
How are you feeling?
Well, I'm fine,
but what brings you out here?
[Dosik] I wanted to apologize
for suspecting you.
So I wanted to sit down
and have a cup of coffee with you.
[Taeju] Yeah.
You're not a very good liar.
If you want to say something, say it.
Once we find Noh Manhui, who's on the run,
this case will be closed.
It's just that…
it doesn't quite add up.
Are you talking about Dr. Ha Jeongsoo?
He said that he was only doing
as he was told.
At first, I thought he was just lying
to save his own skin.
But the evidence fits together too neatly,
like someone set it all up.
I can't put my finger on it,
but it just doesn't feel right.
It's as if I'm missing something.
But then…
your face tells me I'm not the only one.
If you ever think of something,
please let me know.
Okay.
[tense music playing]
[monitor beeping]
If that's the case, I'd like to wait.
Very well. [chuckles]
Thank you, Dr. Ko. We're in your hands.
Honey.
[Dr. Ko] Hmm. [grunts]
[music ends]
STYLE
::cue()
WOORI TOGETHER MEDICAL CENTER
[Dr. Ko sighs]
I believe the incident involving Dr. Ha
has come
as a tremendous shock to all of us,
including our medical staff
and everyone else involved.
[sighs] This case may have come to an end,
but the patients remain uneasy.
Our priority should be
getting the hospital back on track.
Which is why…
[door closes]
My apologies for being late.
Sorry.
Don't mind me.
[Dr. Ko grunts]
Uh…
An arrest warrant has been issued
for Kim Gyeongae,
who is currently our patient.
As soon as she's stable,
she'll be transferred into police custody.
In the meantime,
I'd like Dr. Choi Chiung
to oversee her care.
May I take over?
[tense music playing]
[Dr. Ko] Excuse me?
I was asking
if I could take point
on Kim Gyeongae's case, sir.
Are you being serious right now?
I operated on her.
No one here knows her post-op course
and current condition better than I do.
It makes more sense to keep me on her case
than pulling someone else in.
With everything that's going on,
if you stay on this case,
it'll only get people talking.
Isn't it weirder to change
attending physicians
just because people might talk?
If there's anyone here who knows
about this patient better than I do,
I'm happy to step aside.
Otherwise, I'm staying on her case.
[music intensifies]
How are you feeling?
Wait, what's going on?
What are you doing here?
Acute bleeding developed around the tumor,
so we had to perform an emergency surgery.
The trauma caused the tumor to hemorrhage,
which compressed your nerves.
We were able to drain the blood
and relieve that pressure.
You should start improving now.
Is that what you're here to talk about?
Oh, I'll be your attending physician
starting today.
[scoffs, laughs]
What did you just say?
Thanks to your testimony,
my name was cleared,
-and I'm back at the hospital.
-[scoffs]
It only feels right that I take your case.
Just cut to the chase.
What do you really want?
You said Dr. Ha
planned this whole thing by himself.
But I just don't get it.
The fact that you don't understand it
doesn't make it any less true.
I don't get why Dr. Ha did
what he did to me either.
Remember what you said to me
before your surgery?
STYLE
::cue()
You mean…
"Extending other people's lifespans
by using those unborn babies."
You mean that?
About the fetal stem cells?
How do you know about that?
I signed up for the clinical trial
at this hospital.
That's when I found out
what it was all about.
But who cares, right?
As long as I could get on the list.
At first, I thought,
"How could he call himself a doctor?"
But I was in no position to judge.
What I didn't know
was that he planned
to take advantage of us for his own good.
That answers your question, doesn't it?
This is unfair!
I'm a victim in all of this too!
If I had gotten that surgery,
I wouldn't have taken things this far.
But guess what?
I didn't make the cut.
My life was at stake,
but they made it sound so simple.
There was no rhyme or reason to any of it.
They dropped me from the surgery list
just because I'm an ex-con.
They ruled you out
because of your criminal record?
Who told you that?
Was that Dr. Ha as well?
[mysterious music playing]
Well, what does any of that matter now?
It's all in the past.
You should let it go, Doctor.
All right.
I'll see you on my next rounds.
Take good care of yourself.
[music intensifies]
[music stops]
[Gyeongae] There was no rhyme
or reason to any of it.
They dropped me from the surgery list
just because I'm an ex-con.
[music resumes]
Hey, it's me.
I have a favor to ask.
[music intensifies]
[music ends]
STYLE
::cue()
Hey, Dr. Kang.
What brings you here?
I just had to take a look at something.
I see.
Right, see you around.
[card reader beeps]
[Taeju] Thanks. Appreciate it.
What did you need the lab keycard for?
I just had to look into something.
What was it?
It turns out, Kim Gyeongae signed up
for one of our clinical trials.
-Clinical trial?
-Yeah.
It might have something
to do with your getting kidnapped,
so I wanted to look at some applications
and selection records,
but they weren't there.
I'm sure I've seen them there.
Are you saying someone took them?
Seyun, would you mind
looking into your father's study
and seeing if you find any applications
or selection records in there?
Is that what this was?
Is that why you showed up
at my parents' house?
Is this all…
Is it related to my dad somehow?
[cryptic music playing]
I can't tell you much right now.
Why are you doing this to me again?
You promised me.
You said you'd explain everything
once we got out of there.
I'm sorry.
Is that all you can say?
Forget it. Whatever.
If I look in his study…
and find whatever it is
you're looking for…
you still won't
tell me anything, will you?
[music ends]
[Dr. Cha] Taeju.
[Taeju] Hi, Myeonghui.
[Myeonghui] Good to have you back.
I was so worried.
Thanks for the other night.
Don't mention it.
I trusted you.
I knew you'd never do anything like that.
Are you okay?
You don't look so great.
Yeah, I'm good.
STYLE
::cue()
[news anchor] The rising number of
"lonely deaths" among elderly citizens
living alone has become
a pressing social crisis.
Welcome.
…build a stronger safety net
by implementing smart care services
powered by AI and IoT.
Reporter Kim Jisu has the story.
[Jisu] I'm here at a smart monitoring
center operated by the local government.
Here, you can see
real-time data tracking and status…
Get the one next to it.
…of elderly residents living alone.
If the motion sensors in their homes fail
to detect movement for a set period…
-Yeah, that one works better.
-[Manhui] This one?
[store owner]
Yeah, the blade's way better.
…the alarm goes off.
The government expects this initiative
will allow local authorities
to respond to crises more rapidly
and bridge the gaps
in our current social welfare system.
This is Kim Jisu, reporting for NBS News.
-Here.
-This just in.
The criminal at the center
of national attention…
Are you out to get somebody?
-…of violent offenses…
-How'd you know?
[sore owner] I've seen it all.
It's only in their heads.
Nobody actually has the guts for it.
What about me?
[store owner]
You look like a dreamer indeed.
How much is it?
It's 35,000 won.
…fatally bludgeoning an acquaintance
over a financial dispute.
Given her violent criminal history,
police are…
She was bad news from the beginning.
Why even bother treating trash like her?
They should've just let her die.
That piece of trash
doesn't deserve human rights.
-I swear to God…
-Meanwhile, the third accomplice,
Noh Manhui, remains at large.
He is described as over 180 cm tall
with a heavy, muscular build.
He was last seen wearing
a brown jacket and black pants.
Police warn that Noh is known to be
highly impulsive and is likely armed.
I look way better in person, don't I?
…do not approach him
and contact your local
law enforcement immediately.
You think I'm just a dreamer?
You have a terrible read on people.
-[hammer smashing]
-[store owner screams]
[Dr. Ko] Yeah, come in.
Dad, I brought you some tea.
Thank you. Leave it right there.
How are you feeling these days?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Take it easy, okay?
With everything going on at the hospital,
you must be pretty exhausted, huh?
I'm fine.
-I'll leave you alone now.
-All right.
Well,
has Taeju been giving you a hard time?
Sorry?
Don't let yourself get
dragged into his business.
STYLE
::cue()
[chuckles]
[suspenseful music playing]
WOORI TOGETHER MEDICAL CENTER
CLINICAL TRIAL APPLICATION
[music intensifies]
APPLICANT NAME: OH MINSEOK
APPLICANT: KIM GYEONGAE
GUARDIAN: NOH MANHUI
[Dr. Ko] So how much of a drop
are we talking?
What?
He was stable just this afternoon.
Why are you telling me this now?
Yeah, keep monitoring
Chairman Lee's vitals.
What are you doing here?
Oh, just picking up the tray from earlier.
Don't stay up too late.
Okay.
[door opens, closes]
[siren wailing]
[officer] Out of the way!
SANJEONG HARDWARE
TOOLS, BOLTS NUTS, CONSTRUCTION MATERIALS
[camera shutter clicking]
[Detective Oh] Hello, sir.
Captain.
That thing's shattered.
It's beyond recovery.
[Dosik] Do it the old-fashioned way.
Canvas the area.
-Yes, sir.
-Yeah.
STYLE
::cue()
WOORI TOGETHER MEDICAL CENTER
Ms. Ko.
Dr. Cha.
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
Oh, I heard about what happened.
I can't imagine
how hard it must have been.
I'm all right.
It's amazing that you're already
back at work
after such an ordeal.
I don't think
I could've gotten through it.
[sighs]
Even Taeju…
Everyone seems to be struggling.
"Taeju"?
Have you been talking to my husband?
If you need someone to talk to,
my door is always open.
Does he stop by your office often?
[Myeonghui] I wouldn't say often.
But sometimes, he stops by
to talk about what's on his mind.
About what exactly?
Oh, I guess he doesn't tell you
about our conversations.
Naturally, I assumed
you knew all about it.
Is there anything I should know about?
No, it's just…
I think he's trying to handle
too much on his own.
Had I known he'd never talked
to you about it,
I wouldn't have mentioned it.
Counseling is confidential,
so I can't really share.
I think you guys should
sit down and talk about it.
[elevator dings]
I understand.
[panel beeps]
DIRECTOR KANG TAEJU
NOTE: CLINICAL TRIAL APPLICANT
SCREENED OUT
[knocks on door]
Come in.
Hey, Seyun.
[door closes]
What's this?
It's what you were looking for.
Documents regarding the clinical trial.
Oh, thanks.
And I'm sorry for getting you
involved in all this.
I ran into somebody on my way here.
Who?
Someone you've been
talking to often lately.
[melancholy music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
It was strange.
To find out that someone else knows things
that you've never talked to me about.
-That's--
-It's fine.
I wasn't looking for an explanation.
It's just…
I just can't help but think
that there's so much
I don't know about you.
[music ends]
[phone buzzing]
[eerie music playing]
What's up?
[granddaughter] Ms. Ko just came out
of Dr. Kang's office.
But she didn't look too happy.
I think there's something going on
between the two.
Really?
Look, I can't keep this up, okay?
I did everything that you asked. Please.
If someone ever finds out,
I'll be in huge trouble.
Wouldn't you rather
see your grandma again
while she's still alive?
What did you say?
You didn't do anything to her, did you?
What are you talking about?
I didn't do anything.
Not yet anyway.
[breathing heavily]
I'm not asking for much.
I just need you to be my eyes and ears
and tell me how those two are doing.
But until when?
Today.
It'll be over today.
You got that?
Yeah.
[music ends]
WOORI TOGETHER MEDICAL CENTER
APPLICANT NAME: KIM GYEONGAE
STATUS: SCREENED OUT
[mysterious music playing]
CLINICAL TRIAL APPLICATION
APPLICANT NAME: LEE SEONGUK
STATUS: ACCEPTED
PARK DOHYEON
ACCEPTED
KIM HOJIN
OH MINSEOK
ACCEPTED
SUNG JUIN
[music intensifies]
[Gyeongae] There was
no rhyme or reason to any of it.
-Because I'm an ex-con.
-"Ex-convict."
It doesn't say that anywhere.
[inhales sharply, sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
[sighs]
[music continues]
CALL LOG ANALYSIS REPORT
NAME: KIM GYEONGAE
CHA MYEONGHUI
MAIN BUILDING ELEVATOR #3
[no audible dialogue]
DO NOT CROSS, UNDER INVESTIGATION
SANJEONG HARDWARE
[car owner] I looked when you guys called,
but I wasn't so sure about it.
Okay, give us a sec. We'll look into it.
This freaking bastard.
Is it him?
Yeah, it is.
[Hyeonsu] Wait, stop.
What's the plate number?
[suspenseful music playing]
JEONGHAN GROUP
CEO LEE SEONGUK
"Lee Seonguk."
APPLICANT: LEE SEONGUK
"Park Dohyeon."
"Kim Hojin. Sung Juin."
ILO BIO
CEO PARK DOHYEON
CEO KIM HOJIN
CEO SUNG JUIN
APPLICANT: PARK DOHYEON
ACCEPTED
APPLICANT: KIM HOJIN
APPLICANT: SUNG JUIN
APPLICANT: OH MINSEOK
OH MINSEOK
[music intensifies]
It was all decided from the beginning.
Those people had given up,
but now, they're hopeful
and excited about the future.
Couldn't you just
let them have that hope?
It wasn't about hope.
It was all about money.
[music ends]
STYLE
::cue()
BEHAVIORAL HEALTH
CONSULTATION ROOM
Oh, gosh.
Sorry for dropping in on you like this.
Not at all.
But I've told you
everything I could about Dr. Ha.
What more would you like to know?
Well, we took another look
at the surveillance footage.
Okay.
From the elevator, the day he passed.
You were on the elevator with him.
And I noticed he pressed
the fourth floor at first.
[mysterious music playing]
MAIN BUILDING E/V #3
But then, he changed it
to the basement after you said something.
Um…
Did he really?
I'm not sure.
Yeah, that's what you said
the first time we talked.
That you weren't sure.
Yeah.
And then you asked him if he was okay
because he didn't seem well, right?
Yeah.
But why would Mr. Ha
switch floors after hearing that?
Uh…
That was before you got off.
And after he switched floors,
you said something else to him.
[no audible dialogue]
[Dosik] "Well done,"
you said.
Tell me.
What did you mean by that?
[music continues]
Ah.
But the footage doesn't have any sound.
How are you so sure about what I said?
You know Kim Gyeongae, correct?
I only talked to her during counseling.
That's all.
I think there's more to this story.
You kept in touch with her
until just a month ago.
CHA MYEONGHUI, HA JEONGSOO, NOH MANHUI,
SURVEY, CHA MYEONGHUI
The day Mr. Ha died,
you were in the same elevator.
Plus, your recent contact
with Kim Gyeongae…
Was this all a coincidence?
[music intensifies]
[siren wailing]
We got the location
of Noh Manhui's vehicle.
-He's on the move.
-Where is he?
VEHICLE PLATE NUMBER TRACKING
LICENSE PLATE: 61K 9024
VEHICLE DESC: SILVER SUV
Wait, we need to notify the captain.
61K 9024
[music ends]
[Gyeongae] It's you again.
What do you have for me this time, Doctor?
The real reason
you didn't make it onto the list.
[laughs]
STYLE
::cue()
Okay. So, did you find anything?
It's a list of the top sponsors
of this hospital. Have a look.
The other one's the list of people
who made it into the trial.
The exact same names.
LEE SEONGUK, PARK DOHYEON, OH MINSEOK
It was all about money.
Your life depended on that surgery,
but your fate was set in stone
from the very beginning.
You didn't lose your spot.
You just never had one to begin with.
[somber music playing]
But…
Then why did they tell me
it was because I'm an ex-con?
Who said that?
I couldn't find any records of you
being an ex-con in the application,
so who told you such a lie and why?
Oh, if it wasn't Dr. Ha…
Just my guess.
If someone actually tried to
have you killed through Dr. Ha…
That person is probably very happy
about this current situation.
Do you think that person
will leave you alone now?
[music intensifies]
[phone buzzing]
Yeah, Detective Jang.
What?
Oh, yeah, I understand. Okay.
[phone buzzing]
INCOMING CALL
HUSBAND
[line ringing]
[phone buzzing]
[tense music playing]
-[elevator dings]
-[automated voice] The doors are opening.
CHAIRMAN'S OFFICE
[music intensifies]
WOORI TOGETHER MEDICAL CENTER
STYLE
::cue()
[line ringing]
-[elevator dings]
-[music ends]
WING B, B3
[sighs] Did I leave it upstairs?
[phone buzzing]
INCOMING CALL
HUSBAND
[tires screech]
[buzzing continues]
[gasps]
Ms. Ko.
It's been a while.
Where's Mr. Kang?
MISSED CALL
Don't move, okay?
[gasping]
I said don't move!
THE HUSBAND
[theme music playing]
[Taeju] Who else knows about the hospital
using fetal stem cell samples?
[Dosik] Ms. Cha Myeonghui has fled.
-[Taeju] Myeonghui?
-[Dosik] She's a prime suspect.
[Taeju] Was it Dr. Cha?
The one who lied to you
that your prior got you rejected?
Your husband should know as well.
That you were both used and tossed aside.
So now, you're all by yourself.
[grunts]
[Taeju] Who ordered you to kidnap my wife?
[Manhui] I wasn't after your wife.
It was you.
On whose orders and why?
Translated by Hyun Sik Yoon